Siyuan (Kelvin) Hu

M +86 139 1632 4695 E kelvin.hu.siyuan@amail.com

<u>linkedin.com/in/siyuanhu</u> kelvinuknowhu.github.io

Profile Enthusiastic Software Engineer with expertise in Web Development and Data Visualization.

Offering 1+ years of experience in full software development lifecycle. Quickly learn and master new technologies and enjoy working in both team and self-directed settings.

Education

Cornell University

2017-08 - 2018-12

Ithaca, NY

Master of Engineering in Computer Science

New York University Shanghai

2013-08 - 2017-05

Shanghai, China

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Experience

Blockchain Developer, Dipole Tech

2019-11 - 2020-03

Shanghai, China

Implemented Ethereum smart contracts using Solidity to provide data access and integrated a React-based content management system with Ethereum smart contracts

using Web3 to read and write electric meter data.

Software Engineer I, Uber Advanced Technologies Group

2019-03 - 2019-11

Pittsburgh, PA

Worked under the AVMaps Applications team and focused on building geospatial web tools that enable geo-specialists to produce high-definition maps for self-driving cars. Used React/Redux as the front-end architecture, DeckGL for graphics rendering, and NebulaGL for geometric editing. Other development tools include Jest and Apache Cassandra.

Software Engineer Intern, Uber Advanced Technologies Group

2018-05 - 2018-08

Pittsburgh, PA

Designed and implemented map production web tools for geo-specialists, such as the street-level panorama panel using camera images taken by the in-vehicle cameras and the traffic light labeling tool to collect data for triangulation. Used development tools such

as React, MySQL and Jest on regular basis.

Front End Developer Intern, Energo Labs

2017-01 - 2017-04

Shanghai, China

Developed a management portal using React for a distributed peer-to-peer energy exchange platform to monitor electric meter data, manage user data, and visualize

internal business data.

Skills

Front End Development: HTML5/CSS3/React/Redux/Webpack/Sass/WebGL2

Back End Development: Node.js/Express/MySQL Data Science: D3/Numpy/Pandas/PyTorch/Keras Programming Languages: JavaScript/Python/Java